Guide to the University Christian Movement in New England Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Collected Material, 1955-1980; Series IV
  - Non-UCM Publications
    - New Roots, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 343)
    - New Unity, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 344)
    - Northeast Regional Newsletter, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 345)
    - Odyssey, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 346)
    - Organizing Notes, 1978-1979 (Box 36, Folder 347)
    - Peace Work, 1976-1980 (Box 36, Folder 348)
    - Portland Rag (Box 36, Folder 349)
    - Que Ondee Sola, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 350)
    - Radical Religion, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 351)
    - SCAR, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 352)
    - Seacoast Area Workers' Committee, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 353)
    - Service Employee, 1979-1980 (Box 37, Folder 354)
    - Signs of the Times, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 355)
    - Sister, 1974-1980 (Box 37, Folder 356)
    - Southern Africa, 1977-1979 (Box 37, Folder 357)
    - Southern Africa Support Coalition, 1978-1979 (Box 37, Folder 358)
    - Southern Appalachian Ministry, 1977-1980 (Box 37, Folder 359)
    - Southern Woodcutters Assistance Project, 1979 (Box 37, Folder 360)
    - Strawberry Grenade, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 361)
    - Syracuse Peace Council, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 362)
    - Table Scraps, 1978-1980 (Box 38, Folder 363)
    - TANOD, 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 364)
    - Transverse Poetry, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 365)
    - Toronto Committee for the Liberation of Southern Africa (TCLSAL), 1976-1979 (Box 38, Folder 366)
    - United Methodist Church: Report, 1976-1978 (Box 38, Folder 367)
    - Washington Notes on Africa, 1977-1980 (Box 38, Folder 368)
    - Women's Camp Project, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 369)
    - World Communique, 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 370)
    - Yellow Ribbon, 1973-1976 (Box 38, Folder 371)
- Financial Material, 1952-1975; Series V
  - Accounts payable and receivable, 1952 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Bills, 1969-1970 (Box 39, Folder 372-383)
  - Bills, 1972-1973 (Box 39, Folder 384)
  - Bills, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 385)
  - Bills, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 386)
  - Budget, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 387)
  - Budget, 1972-1973 (Box 40, Folder 388)
  - Budget, 1973-1974 (Box 40, Folder 389)
  - Cash receipts and dispersements, 1944-1947 (Box 45, Folder 2-3)
  - Cash receipts and dispersements, 1947-1948 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Cash receipts and dispersements, 1948-1949 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Cash receipts and dispersements, 1950 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Cash receipts and dispersements, 1951 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Cash receipts and dispersements, 1956 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Cash receipts and dispersements, 1957 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Cash receipts and dispersements, 1958-1959 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Cash receipts and dispersements, 1960-1961 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Cash receipts and dispersements, 1961-1962 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Cash receipts and dispersements, 1963-1964 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Cash receipts and dispersements, 1965-1966 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Cash receipts and dispersements, 1968-1971 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Cash Receipts, 1970 (Box 40, Folder 390)
  - Congregational Church, 1952 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Contributions, 1962-1975 (Box 40, Folder 391-393)
  - Deposit Slips, 1967-1968 (Box 40, Folder 394-395)
  - Deposit Slips, 1969-1975 (Box 41, Folder 396-402)
  - Federal Income Tax, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 403)
  - Finances, 1967-1969 (Box 42, Folder 404-406)
  - Finances: Health Insurance, 1972 (Box 42, Folder 407)
  - Finances: Office Equipment, Telephone, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 408)
  - Finances: Staff Expenses, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 409)
  - Finances: Subscriptions, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 410)
  - Finances: Taxes and Salaries, 1970 (Box 42, Folder 411)
  - Financial Records, 1951-1971 (Box 42, Folder 412-425)
  - Financial Records, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 426)
  - Income, 1967 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Ledger, 1947-1952 (Box 49, Folder 18)
  - Ledgers, 1947-1952 (Box 43, Folder 427-430)
  - Ledger, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 431)
  - Payroll, 1958-1967 (Box 44, Folder 432-436)
  - Savings Account Book, 1958-1973 (Box 44, Folder 437)
  - Tax Papers and Receipts, 1972-1974 (Box 44, Folder 438-440)